

# **PROFILE**

I am a diligent software engineer with 3 years' experience in building back office systems and application development. I believe the best way to solve a problem nowadays is through technology. I am passionate in coding and eager to learn new skills. I constantly seek out innovative solutions to create reliable and user friendly system that enhance business productivity.

### CONTACT

PHONE: 6016-3099552

WEBSITE:

www.haydentan.ml

EMAIL:

Haydentan27@gmail.com

# **HOBBIES**

Tufting rugs.
Learn new skills and languages to create simple application and website.

# TAN SYE SUAN

**SOFTWARE ENGINEER** 

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **WAWASAN OPEN UNIVERSITY**

2018 - 2023

Bachelor of Software Engineering (Honours)

#### **NEXT ACADEMY**

2019

Professional Certificate of Full Stack Web Development Quantum Degree

#### INTERNATIONAL MEDICAL UNIVERSITY

2010 - 2011

Bachelor of Pharmacy (Honours)

#### TUNKU ABDUL RAHMAN UNIVERSITY COLLEAGE

2008 - 2009

A Level / Pre-U in Sciences

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# O2PUS TECHNOLOGY SDN BHD / IXONUS SDN BHD SOFTWARE ENGINEER

2019 - 2022

Develop software application including back office systems with frontend framework and backend API integration based on SRS requirements.

Build backend API with ASP.net, C# and entity framework to create app functionality based on requirement.

Participate in constructing database and manage data from database by writing suitable SQL queries or stored procedures for better application performance.

Restructure and enhancing existing software system to improve the application for better user experience based on client's needs.

Create scalable back office systems for ecommerce application including authentication and authorization for merchant and admin.

# MTREE MARKETING BUSINESS OWNER

2017 - 2019

Retail business in fashion accessories industry.

# MD MANAGEMENT & CONSULTANCY MARKETING MANAGER

2015 - 2017

Responsible to manage company marketing team to help business growth.

Submit documents to government department for foreign workers permit approval.

#### **HRO VISION SDN BHD**

2014 - 2015

### **SENIOR SALES EXECUTIVE**

Responsible to increase company total sales volume by managing sales team to hit monthly sales target.

Manage booth rental and plan for promotional bazaar.

2012 - 2013

### JUNIOR SALES EXECUTIVE

Approaching customers to hit monthly sales target.

### **SKILLS**

Front-end with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, Vue.js and Nuxt.js. Back-end with ASP.net, C#, MVC, Entity Framework Implementation and creation of APIs. Relational database management, MSSQL.